How does this How does this happen to my
我的
glasses?
眼镜怎么会变成这样？
These were on the kitchen counter.
这些物品放在厨房台面上。
How does this happen?
这是怎么发生的？
&gt;&gt; I didn't do it.
我没做。
You put them in the wash all the time.
你经常把它们放进洗衣机里洗。
&gt;&gt; [music and singing]
[音乐和歌声]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; This is the sign that someone had a fun
这是某人昨晚玩得很开心的标志
night last night. Empty bottle of
。 一瓶空
coconut-flavored vodka
椰子味伏特加
and 2/3 of a bottle of orange juice
和三分之二瓶橙汁
gone.
都没了。
&gt;&gt; I feel like I could do something with
我觉得我可以利用
these.
这些做点什么。
They're so official-looking.
它们看起来好正式啊。
What else do I have in here? This camera
这里还有什么其他东西？ 这台相机
that I still don't know how to use.
我到现在都不知道怎么用。
I just keep shuttling it back and forth.
我只是不停地来回搬运。
&gt;&gt; I love it when you come by, but what are
我很高兴你过来，但
you doing here?
你来这里做什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Oh.
哦。
&gt;&gt; I mean, I love it when you stop by.
我是说，我很喜欢你过来。
&gt;&gt; Because I was around the corner.
因为我当时就在附近。
&gt;&gt; Oh, you You don't need anything.
哦，你什么都不需要。
&gt;&gt; No.
不，
&gt;&gt; You're just here to hang out.
你只是来闲逛的。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; Aw.
啊。
You want some fries?
你想吃点薯条吗？
You want some protein pretzels?
想吃点高蛋白椒盐脆饼吗？
Thanks for stopping by.
谢谢光临。   祝你
&gt;&gt; Have a nice day.
今天过得愉快。
&gt;&gt; You never stop by.
你从来不来。
Don't take the elevator.
不要乘电梯。
Bye.
再见。
&gt;&gt; I do love it when she comes to visit.
我非常喜欢她来探望我。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
Mending is better than ending.
修补总比毁灭好。
You know
你知道，
you build a dedicated hotline
你出于非常重要的原因建立了一条专门的热线
to stay in touch for very important
来保持联系，
and then it doesn't work.
结果却发现它不起作用。
&gt;&gt; Your call has been forwarded to
您的来电已转至
voicemail.
语音信箱。
&gt;&gt; Did you call me? I I think Thord and I
你给我打电话了吗？ 我想我和索德要
are going to get lunch. You want to
去吃午饭了。 你想来吗
come?
？
&gt;&gt; How come when I ask I get a wait and
为什么我问了之后总是让你等，
then you now you're going?
然后你又突然说你要走了？
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; How you doing?
你好吗？
&gt;&gt; It's good, bro. Nice day.
挺好的，兄弟。 天气真好。
&gt;&gt; Chilling.
令人不寒而栗。
Special service for me.
为我提供特殊服务。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yep.
。
That is so hostile.
这太恶劣了。
&gt;&gt; We can still sit.
我们还可以坐着。
Thank you. like
谢谢。
Didn't she go like this?
她不是这样走的吗？
You have it in my
你在我的号码里有它。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Wait, how did you go shopping on the
等等，你怎么去巧克力购物的？
Chocolate to the [music] game is good
[音乐]游戏是好的
espresso.
浓缩咖啡。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I got some chocolate.
我弄到了一些巧克力。
All right, this happened yesterday, but
好吧，这件事发生在昨天，但
I don't I think this is interesting. I'm
我认为它并不有趣。 我这就去给
going I'm going to talk you through it,
你讲解，
okay? So, I was on my run yesterday and
好吗？ 昨天我跑步的时候，
I saw that there was a fire on the FDR.
看到罗斯福大道上发生了火灾。
&gt;&gt; Looks like there's a fire on the FDR.
罗斯福大道上好像着火了。
&gt;&gt; The FDR is the main freeway that goes up
FDR高速公路是贯穿
the East Side of the city. [music]
城市东侧的主要高速公路。  [音乐]
And now, I couldn't really see what was
当时，我看不清发生了什么
going on, but I could definitely tell
，但我能肯定地看出有
there was like a car on fire and I could
一辆车着火了，我能
see the flames.
看到火焰。
And then I saw these firefighters like
然后我看到这些消防员就像
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]一样，
&gt;&gt; they kept looking over the side and
他们不停地往下看，
finally they threw over one of their
最后他们扔下了一根
fire hoses. Then the firefighters
消防水带。 然后，
underneath the overpass plugged that
立交桥下的消防员将水管连接
into a hydrant on the ground, which sent
到地面上的消防栓，
water up and onto the overpass. All
水便被输送到立交桥上。
right, at this point I really couldn't
好吧，当时我真的
see what was going on, so I I I ran all
看不清发生了什么事，所以我绕了一圈，
the way around and then ran up the the
然后跑到
Manhattan Bridge so I could see down on
曼哈顿大桥上，这样我就可以清楚地看到下面
what exactly was going on.
到底发生了什么。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; And when I was up there, I met this dude
当我在那儿的时候，我遇到了一个
who didn't speak English, but he had
不会说英语的人，但他
footage on his phone when the like the
手机里有视频，当时
car was really [music] on fire. I think
那辆车真的[音乐]着火了。 我想
it's a Porsche SUV, like a Porsche
那是一辆保时捷SUV，比如保时捷
Cayenne or And I was there for a while.
卡宴之类的。我在那里待了一会儿。
I eventually ran into my friend Mike.
我最终还是碰到了我的朋友迈克。
&gt;&gt; Oh, it's been a long time.
哦，已经很久了。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yes.
。
It's still It's still on fire right now.
现在火势依然很猛。
[music]
[音乐]
But even after like 20 minutes, as I was
但即使过了大约 20 分钟，当我
leaving, I could still see that the car
离开时，我仍然可以看到那辆车
was on fire. [music] Even with all that
着火了。  [音乐] 即使
like fire hosing and all the work the
消防水带喷洒，
firefighters did, that car was still
消防员们也尽了全力，那辆车仍然在
burning.
燃烧。
Imagine how much stuff New York City
想象一下纽约市
firefighters have to deal with.
消防员要处理多少事情。
This sunset is something else. This is
这日落真是美极了。 这
like the first summer sunset of 2026.
就像2026年的第一个夏日落日。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]